Guide to the Nicholas Georgescu-Roegen Papers, 1930-1994 RL.00442
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1930s-1990s; 1
  - Name Files, 1
    - Lozada, Gabriel, 1990-1993 (Box 23)
    - Lucas, Robert, 1978 (Box 23)
    - Lustig, Terry, 1978-1988 (Box 23)
    - Lutz, Mark, 1978-1984 (Box 23)
    - Macmillan Press, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Malinvaud, Edmond, 1976-1978 (Box 23)
    - Malita, Mircea, 1976 (Box 23)
    - Madden, Carl, 1972-1975 (Box 23)
    - Marinov, Hristo, 1977-1981 (Box 23)
    - Mark, Eduard, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Marrama, Vittorio, 1966-1975 (Box 23)
    - Marschak, Jacob, 1956 (Box 23)
    - Martinez Alier, Juan, 1980-1985 (Box 23)
    - Mason, Kenneth, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
    - Matta, Pietro, 1983-1985 (Box 23)
    - Matzner, Egon, 1975-1994 (Box 24)
    - Mayumi, Kozo, 1981-1994 (Box 24)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1963-1981 (Box 24)
    - Meadows, Dennis, 1973-1972 (Box 24)
    - Melet, Regine, 1984 (Box 24)
    - Methodology and Science (Esser, P.H.), 1974-1976 (Box 24)
    - Mermelstein, David, 1984-1985 (Box 24)
    - Merton, Robert K., 1985 (Box 24)
    - Midsouth Academy of Economists, 1973-1975 (Box 24)
    - Miernyk, William, 1977-1994; 2 folders (Box 24)
    - Mihoc, Gheorge, 1971-1980 (Box 24)
    - Miles, Don, 1981-1983 (Box 24)
    - Mirowski, Philip, 1987-1991; 3 folders (Box 24)
    - Miscellaneous Publishers, 1954-1987 (Box 24)
    - Molesti, Romano, 1985-1993 (Box 24)
    - Morishima, Michio, 1964-1982 (Box 24)
    - Moroney, John, 1981-1986 (Box 24)
    - Muldan, Juan Herstajn, undated (Box 24)
    - Murthy, Ranganath, 1985-1988 (Box 24)
    - Murota, Takeshi, 1979-1987 (Box 24)
    - Muse, William W., 1975 (Box 24)
    - Mussard, Jean, 1973-1975 (Box 24)
    - Mutz, Michael (Greenpeace Magazine), 1992 (Box 24)
    - Nakajima, Chihiro, 1986-1987 (Box 24)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1966-1973 (Box 24)
    - National Bureau of Economic Research, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
    - National Science Foundation, 1967-1982 (Box 24)
    - National Science Foundation (Reports), 1964-1970 (Box 24)
    - Nebbia, Giorgio, 1978-1988 (Box 24)
    - Negative Population Growth, 1974-1981 (Box 24)
    - Negoita, Constantin, 1977-1990 (Box 24)
    - Newman, Peter, 1966-1986 (Box 24)
    - Nikaido, H. and Gale, David, 1965 (Box 24)
    - Nuti, D. Mario, 1973 (Box 24)
    - Oak Ridge National Laboratory, 1972-1976 (Box 24)
    - Office of Technology Assessment, 1975-1980 (Box 24)
    - Olivera, Julio H. G., 1968-1971 (Box 24)
    - Olson, Mancur, 1975, 1982 (Box 24)
    - Onicescu, Octav, 1966-1983 (Box 24)
    - Otani, Ryozo, 1966-1984 (Box 25)
    - Oxford University Press, 1973-1974 (Box 25)
    - Ozol, Gengiz, 1973-1985 (Box 25)
    - Pachauri, R. K., 1979-1991 (Box 25)
    - Pearson, Karl, 1931-1932 (Box 25)
    - Pelaez, Carlos, 1972-1976 (Box 25)
    - Pellanda Custoza, Anna, 1978-1980 (Box 25)
    - Penney, Ken, 1981-1982 (Box 25)
    - Pergamon Press, 1974-1989 (Box 25)
    - Perroux, Francois, 1976-1986 (Box 25)
    - Petrovan, Dan, 1961-1968 (Box 25)
    - Peyches, Ivan, 1975 (Box 25)
    - Phipps, Cecil, 1952 (Box 25)
    - Piper, Nikolaus, 1982, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Popescu, Oreste, 1966-1970 (Box 25)
    - President's Commission for a National Agenda for the Eighties, 1980 (Box 25)
    - Prigogine, Ilya, 1977-1978 (Box 25)
    - Princeton University Press, 1975-1986 (Box 25)
    - Prodan, Michail, 1774-1992 (Box 25)
    - Rand McNally Company, 1957-1972 (Box 25)
    - Renaissance Universal Journal, 1979 (Box 25)
    - Resources for the Future (Smith V. Kerry), 1976-1980 (Box 25)
    - Rifkin, Jeremy, 1980-1983 (Box 25)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1957-1976 (Box 25)
    - Roman, Petre (Prime Minister), 1990-1992 (Box 25)
    - Roman, Vatter, 1976-1979 (Box 25)
    - Romanian-American Chamber of Congress, 1991-1993 (Box 25)
    - Romanian Embassy Officials, 1990-1992 (Box 25)
    - Romanian Library in Freiburg, 1969-1987 (Box 25)
    - Roncaglia, Alessandro, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Rugina, Anghel, 1967-1989 (Box 25)
    - Samuelson, Paul, 1953-1989 (Box 25)
    - Scazzieri, Roberto, 1982-1991 (Box 25)
    - Schmidt, Christian, 1973-1978 (Box 25)
    - Schoenman, Jean-Claude, 1968-1991 (Box 25)
    - Schoijet, Mauricio, 1981-1982 (Box 25)
    - Schumpeter, Joseph, 1936 (Box 25)
    - Schutze, Christian, 1989, 1991 (Box 25)
    - Schutts, Francis, 1972-1979 (Box 25)
    - Science Journal, 1977-1981 (Box 25)
    - Seifert, Eberhard K., 1987-1991 (Box 25)
    - Siegfried, John, 1984-1986 (Box 25)
    - Signenza, Manuel, 1976-1983 (Box 26)
    - Silk, Leonard, 1974, 1992 (Box 26)
    - Silveira, Antonio da, 1981-1990 (Box 26)
    - Silver, R. S., 1976-1979 (Box 26)
    - Simonsen, Mario, 1966-1967 (Box 26)
    - Singh, Narindar, 1974-1987 (Box 26)
    - Slesser, Malcolm, 1977 (Box 26)
    - Smutz, Morton, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Snavely, William P., 1968-1969 (Box 26)
    - Soberon, Oscar, 1982-1983 (Box 26)
    - Solo, Robert, 1972-1989 (Box 26)
    - Solterer, Josef, 1971-1973 (Box 26)
    - Sorensen, Phillip and Canterbury, E. Ray, 1974-1976 (Box 26)
    - Sorensen, Torben S., 1975 (Box 26)
    - Southern Economic Association, 1967-1991 (Box 26)
    - Southern Economic Journal, 1974-1987 (Box 26)
    - Spengler, Joseph, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - Spierer, Charles, 1978-1979 (Box 26)
    - Sporea, Constantin, 1967-1988 (Box 26)
    - Sprout, Harold, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Spulber, Nicholas, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Steuer, Max, 1973 (Box 26)
    - Streeten, Paul P., 1973-1990 (Box 26)
    - Swedish Collegium for Advanced Study in the Social Sciences (SCASS), 1992-1993 (Box 26)
    - Sweezy, Paul, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Tamanoi, Yoshiro, 1979-1985 (Box 26)
    - Tanaka, Osamu, 1980-1985 (Box 26)
    - Tani, Piero, 1977-1985 (Box 26)
    - Tarbell, D. Stanley, 1975 (Box 26)
    - Taussig, F. W. (The Quarterly Journal of Economics), 1936 (Box 26)
    - Teichmann, Theodor, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
    - The Tennessean, 1970-1989 (Box 26)
    - Tepicht, Jerzy, 1966-1968 (Box 26)
    - Terrell, William T., 1972-1973 (Box 26)
    - Thrift, Nigel J., 1974-1975 (Box 26)
    - Tintner, Gerhard, 1966-1975 (Box 26)
    - Toyo Keizai Shinposha (Japanese publisher), 1977-1980 (Box 26)
    - Tribus, Myron, 1980-1982 (Box 26)
    - El Trimestre Economico, 1974-1976 (Box 26)
    - Tsuru, Shigeto, 1979-1987 (Box 26)
    - Uhr, Carl G., 1975 (Box 26)
    - Umana, Alvaro, 1984 (Box 26)
    - UNESCO, 1976 (Box 26)
    - U. S. Congress Joint Economic Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 26)
    - U. S. Department of Transportation, 1979-1981 (Box 26)
    - U. S. Information Agency, 1973-1976 (Box 26)
    - U. S. Senate, 1973-1975 (Box 26)
    - University of Ottawa, 1974 (Box 26)
    - Vanderbilt University - Branscomb Award, 1967-1968 (Box 26)
    - Vanderbilt University - Centennial Symposium on Technology and Public Policy, 1975 (Box 27)
    - Vanderbilt University - Graduate Program in Economic Development, no year (Box 27)
    - Vanderbilt University - grants, 1964-1981 (Box 27)
    - Vanderbilt University - internal correspondence, 1949-1982; 6 folders (Box 26)
    - Vanderbilt University - mathematics minor committee, 1972 (Box 27)
    - Vanderbilt University - salary negotiations, 1951-1975 (Box 27)
    - Vanderbilt University - parking rage, 1967-1972 (Box 27)
    - Veziroglu, T. Nejat, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Vietorisz, Thomas, 1974 (Box 27)
    - Villela, Villanova, 1972-1973 (Box 27)
    - Vyasulu, Vinod, 1973-1983 (Box 27)
    - Wade, Nicholas, 1975-1988 (Box 27)
    - Wagensberg, Jorge, 1978-1980 (Box 27)
    - Walter Eucken Institut, 1986-1990 (Box 27)
    - Webb, Samuel, 1976 (Box 27)
    - Weiss, Roger, 1967-1991 (Box 27)
    - Western Economic Association, 1987 (Box 27)
    - Whitaker, John, 1983 (Box 27)
    - Whitley, Richard, 1979-1980 (Box 27)
    - Williamson, Jeffrey G., 1968 (Box 27)
    - Wilson, Kenneth D., 1975-1978 (Box 27)
    - Winninghof, Ellie, 1992 (Box 27)
    - Winston, Gordon, 1971-1974 (Box 27)
    - Wold, Herman, 1972-1975 (Box 27)
    - Wolfson, Murray, 1968-1973 (Box 27)
    - World Council of Churches, 1974 (Box 27)
    - World Organization of General Systems and Cybernetics, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
    - Woo, Henry K. H., 1988 (Box 27)
    - Wu, Shih-Yen, 1971 (Box 27)
    - Zamagni, Stefano, 1976-1991 (Box 27)
    - Zamfirescu, Ioana-Paul, 1976-1979 (Box 27)
    - Zeleny, Milan, 1977-1985 (Box 27)
    - Zeman, Jirl, 1972-1976 (Box 27)
  - Alphabetical Files, 2
    - A-K, 1952-1994; 12 folders (Box 27)
    - L-Z and undated, 1955-1994; 16 folders (Box 28)
  - Assorted General Correspondence, 3
    - Letters of recommendation for students, 1950-1989; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Letters to the Editor, 1980-1990 (Box 28)
    - Reprint permission requests, 1975-1984 (Box 28)
    - Requests for reprints, 1950-1976; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Fan mail, 1950-1976; 6 folders (Box 28)
    - Fan mail, 1977-1993; 4 folders (Box 29)
  - Romanian Correspondence, 4
    - Undated Romanian letters (Box 29)
    - Unsorted Romanian letters, 1967-1994; 29 folders (Box 29)
- Audiovisual materials, 1963-1975 and undated; 1
  - Economics Dinner Tape, 1975-10-24; 1
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0001)
  - 14-17 New, undated; 2
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0002)
  - 25-27 new, undated; 3
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0003)
  - Beethoven Piano, undated; 4
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0004)
  - 198 Beethoven Piano Music Vol. I II, undated; 5
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0005)
  - 298 Schubert Quintet D956 C, undated; 6
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0006)
  - I. 370 || 270 5/5 5/9, undated; 7
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0007)
  - 439 | 2. || 65 || 325 ||, undated; 8
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0008)
  - 387 Opera Tri La Gioconda, undated; 9
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0009)
  - unlabeled, undated; 10
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0010)
  - 315 Bartok Crn Str no. 1, no. 5, undated; 11
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0011)
  - 17-20, undated; 12
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0012)
  - New 39-42, undated; 13
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0013)
  - 65 Mozart Don Giovanni, 1963-01; 14
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0014)
  - 66 Mozart Don Giovanni, 1964-02; 15
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0015)
  - 1. 362x 2. 307 Mozart 387, undated; 16
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0016)
  - 43-46 New, undated; 17
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0017)
  - 32-34 New, undated; 18
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0018)
  - 28-31 New, undated; 19
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0019)
  - 307 4/7/58 7/4/58, undated; 20
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0020)
  - 387, undated; 21
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0021)
  - 51-53 New, undated; 22
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0022)
  - 18-21 part new, undated; 23
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0023)
  - 244 BARROC, undated; 24
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0024)
  - Rachmaninoff Rapsody Paganini, 263, undated; 25
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0025)
  - 281 x || 482, undated; 26
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0026)
  - 33-34, undated; 27
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0027)
  - 8-12, undated; 28
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0028)
  - 3/17/58 3/28/58, undated; 29
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0029)
  - 25-29, undated; 30
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0030)
  - Reo Plastic Lender 3:00, undated; 31
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0031)
  - Music of Johann Strauss, undated; 32
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0032)
  - Last 1969/70, undated; 33
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0033)
  - 18-13 new, undated; 34
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0034)
  - 6-9 new, undated; 35
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0035)
  - 22-24 new, undated; 36
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0036)
  - 30, 32, undated; 37
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0037)
  - 1-5 / 2, undated; 38
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0038)
  - unlabeled, undated; 39
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 30, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0039)
  - 4/14/58 4/18, undated; 40
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0040)
  - 140 A51 262, undated; 41
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0041)
  - Schubert Sym 5, 8, 9, undated; 42
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0042)
  - unlabeled, undated; 43
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0043)
  - unlabeled, undated; 44
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0044)
  - 47-50 New, undated; 45
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0045)
  - 25-28, undated; 46
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0046)
  - 2x? 786, undated; 47
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0047)
  - 213, undated; 48
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0048)
  - 1-4/1969, undated; 49
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0049)
  - 13-16, undated; 50
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0050)
  - New 35-38, undated; 51
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0051)
  - unlabeled, undated; 52
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0052)
  - Akai Demonstration Tape, undated; 53
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0053)
  - Interview with Prof. Nicholas-Georgescu Roegen 7.13.67, 1967-07-13; 54
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0054)
  - unlabeled, undated; 55
    - Original 1/4" open reel tape (Box 31, Audio-reel RL00442-RR-0055)